



CURRICULUM VITAE

My name is Mattia Marsetti and I was born in the Alps. After playing with the famous bricks for almost a decade I dedicated my teens in mastering Latin and Greek, while self-teaching informatics. Then I found my way into Engineering and, at the same time, I felt the need to explore what was not modeled by an equation with various volunteering experiences. I'm currently working on the Powertrain SW that runs inside the Ferrari GT and Motorsport cars.

E.

WORK EXPERIENCES

MOTORSPORT SW SPECIALIST – Corse Clienti	2020 - now
SW Development, Integration and Testing	
Ferrari - Maranello	

2017-2020

2014-2017

POWERTRAIN CONTROL ENGINEER – GT Cars
Set up of the SW Sharing environment with the Supplier and SW
Development from Requirements to Tests
Ferrari - Maranello



EDUCATION

Politecnico di Milano - Milano	2011-2016	
HIGH CCHOOL Distance It was to the Classical	D006 D044	

HIGH SCHOOL – Diploma di maturità Classica 2006-2011 Liceo G. Piazzi - Sondrio



VOLUNTEER

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Phone operator & visits to the hospital for CasAmica - Milano	
REFUGEE EMERGENCY OPERATOR logistics, transportations for CARITAS – Palermo Integration project for a refugee family – Sondrio	LUG-AUG 2014 - 2017

EDUCATOR
Kids education for Centro di Apojo Infanto Juvanil – Corumbà (Brazil)

LUG-AUG
2013



SKILLS

- SW DEV. & DATA ANALYSIS: mainly Matlab/Simulink, often EXCEL, always GIT
- PLAN & PROCESS DEV: Agile Development in JIRA and SW Life-Cyle Development with Polarion
- CALIBRATION/DEBUG: expert in the use of CRETA INCA MDA ECU Diagnostics

CONTACTS

(+39) 349 167 2584

marsigliomarsetti@gmail.com

Via Caggiati 2, Reggio Emilia (IT)

ON THE WEB

in Linkedin

NO Twitter/Facebook/Instagram

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN

· native

ENGLISH

fluent

INTERESTS

Books and Comics
Board games
Analogue Photography
Snowboard

PRIVACY

In compliance with the GDPR and the Italian Legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document

Version: 1.23